toshibadirect.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy Statement (“Privacy Statement”) applies solely to the online information gathering and data sharing practices of Toshiba America Information Systems, Inc. ("Toshiba") for this Web Site, service and/or application (“Toshiba Online”) and does not apply to other Toshiba affiliates or our parent company, and such entities may have their own privacy policies.

Your privacy is important to Toshiba. This statement provides you with information about the type of personally identifiable information that is gathered and tracked through Toshiba Online, how the information is used, stored, secured and with whom the information is shared. In general, you can visit Toshiba via Toshiba Online without providing any information about yourself. However, there might be times when we may need information from you or we obtain information about you when you or others provide us with such information. By using Toshiba Online, you agree to the terms provided in this Privacy Statement. 

## Collection of Personal Information

We may collect your name, address, e-mail address, domain name, client IP address, phone number, and other personally identifiable information about you ("personal information") and the products or services you purchase or obtain from us. This information is collected, in general, from information you provide to us through Toshiba Online when you complete a product registration or initial setup wizard, through your survey responses or rebate forms, and/or through your filling out and submitting forms through Toshiba Online requesting information from Toshiba.

With your consent, we may also collect your precise geographic location information via Toshiba Online.

## Access to Your Information and Opting Out

You may opt out of receiving marketing information from us by unsubscribing using the link on any email you receive from us. If you opt out of receiving our marketing information, we may still send you certain types of communications, such as product updates for your registered products, transactional or legal notification emails, warranty related communications and we may respond to requests from you by email. We will try to process your opt out request within ten business days.

Although via Toshiba Online we may collect personal information about your online activities using Toshiba Online over time, we do not collect such information from you about your activities on third party web sites. We do not respond to “do not track” signals, if any, being sent from your browser. Furthermore, we permit select third parties to collect non-personal information about your online activities over time and across different web sites when you use Toshiba Online. If you would like to opt-out of any of the technologies that we and/or our third parties employ to collect your information via Toshiba Online (e.g. cookies), you may do so by blocking, deleting, or disabling them as your browser or device permits. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about your browser settings and how to handle cookies.

For more information on third-party advertising-related cookies and how to exercise your choice to opt-out of them, please visit <http://www.aboutads.info/choices> and/or [www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Use and Sharing of Personal Information

We do not sell your personal information. We may use your personal information to contact you about products you have purchased, inform you of product and service opportunities that may be of interest to you, to conduct market research regarding Toshiba products or services, to customize the content of Toshiba Online for you, to support and enhance our communications with you, or for other business purposes. We may share your personal information within the Toshiba family of companies for business purposes and with other companies who provide marketing or other services on our behalf and at our direction, but we do not permit them to use such personal information that we have shared for their own direct marketing purposes. We may share your personal information outside of the Toshiba family with companies in connection with your trial, purchase or registration of products or services provided by such companies and with companies that perform marketing or other services on our behalf and at our direction. We may engage third parties to help deliver Toshiba ads, offers and other online communications. These companies may collect and use information about you to help us better understand the effectiveness of our offers, promotions and types of advertising that appeal to our customers. Third party service providers and suppliers that are providing services for us are required to keep confidential the information received on behalf of Toshiba and are not to use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for us. We may enhance or merge your information collected online with other information you provide us through other sources including but not limited to product registration, call centers, rebate programs, sweepstakes, surveys, or data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.

We may share your personal information if the disclosure is done as a part of a purchase, transfer or change of control of our products and/or services or our assets (e.g., in the event that all or substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, personal information may be one of the transferred assets).

We may also share your personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, and other legal action, or if Toshiba reasonably believes it is appropriate to do so to protect Toshiba, its customers or the public.

## Cookies and Various Technologies

We use technology to help us deliver customized visitor experiences and understand trends and patterns.

We may engage third parties to collect non-personal information using "cookies" and/or other industry standard technologies (e.g., clear GIFS, web beacons, pixel tags, javascript tag) to generate statistics or measure and analyze website activity (including page usage and paths followed during visits through our sites and/or the items you view or place in your shopping bag) in order to improve Toshiba Online functionality, deliver content specific to you and/or targeted for your interests while using Toshiba Online and/or a third party web site, and to better manage advertising of our products. The collected data also helps us determine which product, service or support information may be appropriate for you and to help us maintain an efficient shopping experience for you.

You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a "cookie" or to turn off "cookies" completely. If you do so, however, some areas of our site may not function properly.

## Information Security

Toshiba protects the quality and integrity of your personal information in accordance with commercially reasonable standards. While Toshiba strives to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

## Third Party Web Sites

Toshiba Online may contain links to other third party web sites that are not operated by us. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party web sites. The information practices of those third party web sites are not covered by this Privacy Statement. Other Toshiba co-branded web sites may also operate under their own privacy and security policies. You are responsible for reviewing third party and co-branded privacy policies, as applicable, to determine the handling of your information.

## Children's Privacy

Toshiba does not seek to collect personal information about children through Toshiba Online. If you are under the age of 18, please do not provide any personally identifiable information to us through Toshiba Online.

## Notification of Changes

From time to time, we may choose to change our privacy practices and this Privacy Statement. We will notify you of material changes to the Privacy Statement by posting a revised Privacy Statement via Toshiba Online with an updated effective date. We recommend that you check back at Toshiba Online at www.us.toshiba.com/website/privacy-policy on a periodic basis to review the then current Privacy Statement. Any updates, revisions, supplements, modifications or amendments to this Privacy Statement shall be effective immediately upon its posting via Toshiba Online and will only be applicable to disputes arising, or arising out of events occurring, after such posting has been made. You agree that you will continue to be bound by this Privacy Statement, however and whenever it is updated, revised, supplemented, modified, or amended, if you continue to use Toshiba Online after, the updates, revisions, supplements, modifications or amendments have been posted.

## Questions regarding our privacy statement

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or our privacy practices, please contact us at: tais-privacy@toshiba.com. This Privacy Statement is effective as of **May 16, 2016**.

© 2004-2017 Toshiba America Information Systems, Inc.
